This is Zero
One Alpha. We have secured Falcon.
I say again,
we have secured Falcon.
Grenade! Sir, get back!
Shit.
Fucking missed it.
How did I
fucking miss it?
Merlin, I apologize for
putting you in this position.
You trained him well.
James...
training is over.
Welcome to Kingsman.
Lancelot.
Sir.
I'll deal with
this mess personally.
I very much regret that
your husband's bravery
can't be publicly celebrated.
I hope you understand.
How can I understand?
You won't
tell me anything.
I didn't even know
he wasn't with his squad.
I'm so sorry,
I can't say more.
But I would like to present you
with this Medal of Valor...
and if you look closely on
the back, there's a number.
And as a more concrete
gesture of our gratitude...
we'd like to offer you, um...
Let's call it a favor.
The nature of it
is your choice.
Just tell the operator...
"oxfords not brogues, "
and then I'll know it's you.
I don't want your help!
I want
my husband back!
What's your name,
young man?
Eggsy.
Hello, Eggsy.
Can I see that?
You take care of this,
Eggsy.
All right?
And take care
of your mum, too.
So sorry, Professor Arnold.
Just a tiny bit more.
Oh, for God's sakes,
just rip it off.
I'm under very strict
instructions not to hurt you.
Look, you've made a mistake.
I'm a university lecturer.
I've got no money.
This isn't about money.
Our boss just
wants to talk to you.
Am I meant to
find that reassuring?
He'll be here soon.
He'll explain.
Do you like whiskey?|
Red, get the '62 Marmoreal.
Hmm.
Honestly, this whiskey,
it's amazing.
You will shit.|
I suppose asking to borrow a cup
of sugar is a step too far?
Professor Arnold,
I'm here to take you home.
Hmm.
1962 Marmoreal.
It'd be a sin
to spill any.
Don't you think?
Can you hold these?
Please?
Thank you.
Everything is clean.
My kind of welcome.
Mmm.
No stomach for violence.
I mean, literally,
I see one drop of blood...
that is me done.
I'm like...|
projectile.
Listen, I'm so sorry...
you had to witness all this unpleasantness
due to our uninvited guest.
But I promise you, by the time
I've found out who he works for...
you and I will be
the best of friends.
To the shop, please.
Arthur's in the
dining room, sir.
Arthur.
Galahad.
The others were
beginning to wonder
if we were going to
have a double toast.
Gentlemen, I'm thankful to
say it's been 17 years...
since we last had occasion
to use this decanter.
Lancelot was an outstanding
agent, and a true Kingsman.
He will be sorely missed.
To Lancelot.
I intend to start the
selection process for
Lancelot's replacement
tomorrow.
I want each of you
to propose a candidate...
and have them report
to UK HQ...
no later than 9 p. m. GMT.
Thank you.
Merlin.
Come in.
Lancelot was investigating
a group of mercenaries...
who were experimenting
with biological weaponry.
Glasses, gentlemen, please.
Uganda, 2012.
Synthetic nothingness.
They put it in the water supply
of a guerrilla army base.
Rage, cannibalism,
multiple fatalities.
Chechnya, 2013.
Insurgents turned on
one another.
Indisputably, the work
of our mercenaries,
but no trace of any
chemicals of any kind.
So what happened
to Lancelot?
He tracked them to this
property in Argentina.
While he had them
under surveillance...
he became aware
they'd effected a kidnapping.
So he executed a solo rescue
mission, which failed.
This is his
last transmission.
Who is he? Some climate
change doomsayer.
Expounds something
called "Gaea theory"...
about the world healing
itself, or some such.
But what's curious,
is he's not actually missing.
This is Professor Arnold...
at Imperial College
this morning.
It's all yours.
And don't forget
your membership proposal.
Try picking a more suitable
candidate this time.
17 years and still...
evolving with the times remains an
entirely foreign concept to you.
Need I remind you,
I wouldn't be here
if it weren't for
that young man?
He was as much Kingsman
material as any of them.
More so.
But he wasn't exactly
one of us, was he?
Let's face it,
Galahad,
your little
experiment failed.
With respect, Arthur,
you're a snob.
"With respect"?
The world is changing.
There's a reason why aristocrats
developed weak chins.
Eggsy?
Eggsy, come here.
Got any Rizal, babe?
No.
Why don't you do
your mum a favor,
go down to the shop
and get some?
Get them yourself.
Oi.
What have I said to you about
speaking to Dean like that?
Three's a crowd, innit?
Why don't Dean's poodle go?
I'll tell you what.
Why don't you take this,
go and get some Rizal...
get yourself some sweets?
And while you're gone...
we'll show your mother how three
can be good company.
Thanks, babe.
There we go.|
Is that better?
If Dean treats
your mum so bad,
why doesn't she
leave him?
Low self-esteem.
That's her problem.
Fuck off. Why would she
have low self-esteem?
Peggy's mum is well fit.|
No offense, Brut.
It's all right.
One of these days,
I'm gonna smash his face in.
Are you mental, cuss?
He'd just get
that lot to do you,
and then pretend
he knew nothing--
... about it.
Oi! You think you can chat shit
about us and we won't do nothing...
just because our guvnors
banging Peggy's mum?
Pretty much, yeah.
Brut, just leave it.
Let's just go, man.
It's not worth it.
You boys have
outstayed your welcome.
Leave.
What?
I'm sorry about that, Brut.
Yeah.
Mug.
They weren't fucking
worth it, boys.
It's freezing.
Why are we walking?
You jacked his
fucking car keys, Brut?
Yeah. Now, we're gonna nick his car.|
Shit!
Hold on, boys.
Hey, that's my fucking car!
Hey! Hey! Eggsy!
I swear, you want to
fucking stop it!
You're a fucking dead man!
Stop it!
I'm gonna fucking have ya!
Floor it, Eggsy!|
Floor it!|
Wanker!
Yeah, Dean.
Look, it's me.
Eggsy just stole
my fucking car, yeah.
I've come out the pub, he's done
15 donuts in my fucking face...
and he's drove off.
No, I can't have it!
He's disrespecting me.
And that means,
he's disrespecting you.
Hold up! What the... ?
Oh.
Dickhead.
Foxes are vermin, cuss.
Should've driven it over.
Should've done
a lot of things.
I'll sort this.
Get out of the car.
I said, get out
of the fucking car!
Eggsy, there is no such
thing as honor amongst thieves.
Now, you can start giving me some
names of the boys you were with...
or you go down.
It's up to you.
I want to exercise
my right to a phone call.
Well, I hope it's
to your mum...
to tell her you're gonna be 18
months late for your dinner.
Customer Complaints,
how may I help you? Um...
My name's Eggsy Unwind.
Sorry, Gary Unwind.
And I'm up shit creek.
I'm in Lowborn
police station...
and my mum said to call this
number if ever I needed help.
I'm sorry, sir.
Wrong number.
Wait! Wait!
Oxfords not brogues.
Your complaint has been
duly noted...
and we hope that we have not
lost you as a loyal customer.
Yeah.
You what?
I...
Yeah.
Yes, I totally understand.
Eggsy.
Would you like
a lift home?
Who are you?
The man who
got you released.
That ain't an answer.
A little gratitude
would be nice.
My name is Harry Hart,
and I gave you that medal.
Your father saved my life.
So before you was a
tailor, was you in the army?
Like an officer.
Not quite.
So where was you posted,
Iraq or something?
Sorry, Eggsy. Classified.
But my dad
saved your life, yeah?
The day your father died,
I missed something.
And if it weren't
for his courage...
my mistake would have cost the
lives of every man present.
So I owe him.
Your father was
a brave man.
A good man.
And having read
your files...
I think he'd be bitterly disappointed
in the choices you've made.
You can't talk to me
like that.
Huge I. Q.
Great performance
at primary school.
And it all went tits up.
Drugs, petty crime.
Never had a job.
You think there's a lot of jobs
going around here, do you?
Doesn't explain why you
gave up your hobbies.
First prize, regional
Under-10s gymnastics...
two years in a row.
Your coach had you pegged
as Olympic team material.
Yeah, well, when you grow up around
someone like my stepdad...
you pick up
new hobbies pretty quick.
Of course.
Always someone ease뭩 fault.
Who's to blame
for you quitting the Marines?
You were
halfway through training,
doing brilliantly,
but you gave up.
Because my mum went mental.
Banging on about losing me
as well as my dad.
Didn't want me being cannon
fodder for snobs like you.
Judging people like me
from your ivory towers...
with no thought about
why we do what we do.
We ain't got much choice.
You get me?
And if we was born with the same
silver spoon up our arses...
we'd do just as well as you.
If not, better.
What the fuck you doing here?
You taking the piss?
Some more examples
of young men...
who simply need
a silver suppository?
No, they're exceptions.
Come on.
Nonsense. We haven't
finished our drinks.
After you nicked his car...
Dean says you're fair game.
He don't give a shit
what your mum says.
Um, listen, boys...
I've had a rather
emotional day...
so whatever your beef
with Eggsy is,
and I'm sure
it's well-founded...
I'd appreciate it
enormously...
if you could just
leave us in peace...
until I finish
this lovely pint of Guinness.
You should get out
of the way, Granddad,
or you'll get
hurt and all.
He ain't joking.
You should go.
Mmm.
Excuse me.
If you're looking for
another rent boy,
they're on the
corner of Smith street.
Manners...
market...
man.
Do you know
what that means?
Then let me
teach you a lesson.
Are we going to stand around here
all day, or are we going to fight?
You fucking dirty,
fucking dirty--
Sorry about that.
Needed to let off
a little steam.
I heard yesterday
a friend of mine died.
He knew your father too,
actually.
Now, I do apologize, Eggsy.
I shouldn't have done this in front of you.|
No, please! I won't
say nothing, I swear!
If there's one thing I can do,
it's keep my mouth shut.
You won't tell a soul?
Ask the feds.
I've never grassed anyone up.
Is that a promise?
On my life!
Much appreciated, Eggsy.
You're right about
the snobs.
But there, too,
there are exceptions.
Best of luck
with everything.
In celebrity news,
the Richmond Valentine movie
premiered in Hollywood last night.
The story of the internet
billionaire's rise to power...
is expected to be this
award season's hot ticket.
One notable absence from the
red carpet was Ciggy Azalea...
still missing three days after she
failed to appear at her Oakland concert.
No ransom has been demanded.
Eggsy, just go, please, because
he's gonna...
No,
please, don't hurt him!
Fuck off! Get the fuck away
with ya!
Shut the fuck up!
Who was with you
in that fucking pub?
I want to know the name of
the geezer you was with.
I wasn't with no one!
Who was it?
I don't know what you're on about.
I don't know
who you're fucking on about!
Fucking tell me his name!
I don't know who you're
fucking on about!
You listen to me!
I want to know who you was with
in that pub. Do you understand?
I want to know his fucking name!
Because, I swear,
I'll rip your head off.
Tell me!
I don't know
what you're fucking on about!
Just tell him, Eggsy!
Fuck off! Fuck off, Michelle!|
I could kill you
right now...
and no one in the whole world
will notice!
But I would.
I have enough evidence
on your activities...
to have you locked up
for the rest of your life...
Mr. Dean Anthony Baker.
What the fuck?
So I suggest you
leave the boy alone...
or I shall be forced to deliver it
to the appropriate authorities.
Eggsy, meet me at the tailor
I told you about.
What the fuck's
going on here?
Eggsy, you fucking maggot!
Hey, we got a racer!
Come here. Hey!
Eggsy, you fucking--
Come here, son!
You wanker!
I'll have you, son!
I've never met
a tailor before.
But I know you ain't one.
Come with me.
Come on in.
What do you see?
Someone who wants to know
what the fuck is going on.
I see a young man
with potential.
A young man
who is loyal.
Who can do
as he's asked.
And who wants to do
something good with his life.
Did you see the film
Trading Places?
No.
How about Nikita?
Pretty Woman?
All right.
My point is, that the
lack of a silver spoon
has set you
on a certain path...
but you needn't stay on it.
If you're prepared to adapt
and learn, you can transform.
Oh, like in My Fair Lady.
Well, you're
full of surprises.
Yes, like My Fair Lady.
Only, in this case,
I'm offering you
the opportunity to
become a Kingsman.
A tailor?
A Kingsman agent.
Like a spy?
Of sorts.
Interested?
You think I've got
anything to lose?
Since 1849...
Kingsman tailors have clothed the
world's most powerful individuals.
By 1919, a great number
of them had
lost their heirs
to World War One.
That meant a lot of money
going inherited.
And a lot of powerful men with a desire
to preserve peace and protect life.
Our founders realized that they could
channel that wealth and influence...
for the greater good.
And so began
our other venture.
An independent, international
intelligence agency...
operating at the
highest level of discretion.
Above the politics
and bureaucracy...
that undermine the integrity of
government-run spy organizations.
The suit is a
modern gentleman's armor.
And the Kingsman agents
are the new knights.
How deep does this
fucking thing go?
Deep enough.
Shit, we're late.
Your father had the
same look on his face.
As did I.
Come on.
Galahad.
My code name.
Late again, sir.
Good luck.
In you go.
Fall in.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my name is Merlin.
You are about to embark...
on what is probably the most dangerous
job interview in the world.
One of you,
and only one of you,
will become the next Lancelot.
Can anybody tell me
what this is?
Yes?
Body bag, sir.
Correct. Charlie, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
Good.
In a moment, you will
each collect a body bag.
You will write your name
on that bag.
You will write the details of
your next of kin on that bag.
This represents your acknowledgment of
the risks that you are about to face...
as well as your agreement
to strict confidentiality.
Which, incidentally, if you
break, will result in you...
and your next of kin...
being in that bag.
Is that understood?
Excellent
Fall out.
Roxanne.
But call me Roxy.
I'm Eggsy.
"Eggsy"?
No "Eggsy".
Eggo?
Where did they dig you up?
You know we're not allowed
to discuss who proposed us.
No need to bite
his head off.
Charlie's only making
conversation, right, Charlie?
Hmm.
I'm Digby.
Digby.
Eggo, this is Rufus.
Rufus, Eggsy.
So, Eggo, are you
Oxford or Cambridge?
Neither.
Saint Andrews?
Durham?
No, wait, I think
we may have met.
Did you serve me at the McDonald's
in Winchester service station?
No.
But if I had,
I would have given you
an extra helping
of secret sauce.
It's definitely Saint
Andrews
Just ignore them.
You need a pen?
Cheers.
Amelia, isn't it?
Amelia, Eggsy-
Hi, Eggsy-
Don't take any notice
of those guys.
That's what I told him.
It's just scare tactics.
Classic army technique.
No one's gonna die.
Shame.
Great. You don't
know, the CIA don't know.
Nobody knows who this guy is?
Fine.
Seriously, it's fine.
Well, it's not really fine,
but it's not why I'm here.
Hell, man, you know me.
Money's not my issue.
I could've retired
straight out of MIT...
fucked off to some island,
let the business run itself.
Nobody told me
to try and save the planet.
I wanted to.
Climate change research, lobbying,
years of study, billions of dollars...
and you know why I quit?
Because the last time I checked,
the planet was still fucked.
Hence, my epiphany-
Money won't solve this.
Those idiots who
call themselves politicians...
have buried their heads in the sand and
stood for nothing but re-election.
So I spent the last two years
trying to find a real solution.
And I found it.
Now, if you really want to make
the world a better place...
I suggest you open
your fucking ears,
because I'm about to
tell it to you.
Go on, Mr. Valentine.
I'm still listening.
As long as you
agree to all my terms.
All right, no one panic.
Listen to me.
Stay calm.
Fuck.
Loo snorkels,
loo snorkels!
Loo snorkels?
Showerheads!
Showerheads?
She's right.
Fucking go!
Hey, hang about, what's wrong
with the fucking door?
Congratulations on
completing your first task.
Charlie, Roxy, well done.
For those of you
who are still confused...
if you can get a breathing tube
around a U-bend of a toilet...
you have an
unlimited air supply.
Simple physics,
worth remembering.
Eggsy, well done for spotting
that was a two-way mirror.
He's probably seen
enough of them.
Yeah, you can all wipe
those smirks off your faces.
Because as far
as I'm concerned,
every single one of you
has failed.
You all forgot
the most important thing...
teamwork.
So much for
classic army technique.
35.
105.
That's it. That's it.|
Hello.
Can I help you?
Yes. I have a question
about anthropogenic force.
Oh. Really? It's
actually quite fascinating.
My colleague died
trying to rescue you...
and I'm sure you saw
how well trained he was...
so I suggest you tell me who kidnapped
you and why they let you go.
I have no idea
what you're talking--
I'm not supposed to say it,
but it was--
Oh, for God's sake,
I've barely touched you.
Oh, man up!|
Fuck that guy, whoever he is.
I'm gonna--
He made me kill
Professor Arnold.
I goddamn loved
Well, the good news is...
we know the emergency
and surveillance system work.
You know what's
not good news?
"My colleague died!"
That's what he said!
This is an organization,
and they're all over us.
Whoever you spoke to--
I told you...
I made contact with the KGB,
MI6, Mossad and Beijing.
They all insist
he wasn't one of theirs.
Beijing-
So freaky how there's no recognizable
name for the Chinese secret service.
Now, that's what you call
a secret, right?
You know what? Fuck it.
We need to speed things up.
Bring the
product release forward.
We're only halfway
into production...
and speeding it will
cost a fortune.
Do I look like
I give a fuck?
Just get it done.
As some of you will
have learned last night...
teamwork is paramount
here at Kingsman.
We're here to enhance your
skills, test you to the limit.
Which is why you're
gonna pick a puppy.
Wherever you go,
your dog goes.
You will care for it.
You will teach it.
And by the time it's fully
trained, so will you be.
Those of you
who are still here, that is.
Do you understand?
Choose VOW PUPPY-
A poodle?
What?
They're gun dogs.
Oldest working breed.
Easy to train.
A pug?|
It's a bulldog, innit?
It'll get bigger,
though, won't it?
Shit.
His MRI shows
no signs of concussion.
No direct
brain trauma at all.
How much longer
can he be out?
That's the
million-dollar question.
We don't know what he was
exposed to in there.
What about Harry's footage?
It didn't stream
to his home terminal.
Encrypted and uncrackable.
If and when
he comes around...
you might want to have a with
him about sharing his password.
Is he gonna be all right?
We need to
have patience, . .
But there's hope, okay?
If I were you, I'd concentrate
on your training.
Make it through the tests.
Make him proud.
Come on,
come on, come on!
J. B. , come on! Come on!|
I'm not coming last
because of you.
J. B. , I'll shoot you! Goddamn
you, I'll fucking shoot you!
Merlin said we're not
allowed to hold you.
Bollocks.
Water!|
Come on, then!
Eggsy, forget it!
What's wrong, mate?
You can't take a joke?
Seriously, you'll get thrown
out, and it's just not worth it.
Maybe I don't give a fuck
if I get kicked out!
Do it. Come on, you pleb.
Charlie, fuck off!
Aw.
Yeah, go on, walk away.
Dickhead.
Come on, J. B.
Come on, good boy.
You have exactly one
hour to complete the test...
starting now.
New target,
800 meters.
You know, it's unbelievable.
You're still here...
lingering like some big, steaming
shit that just won't flush.
Roger that.
Target identified.
And how about you
shut the fuck up?
Positive discrimination...
that's what it is.
It's like those fucking
state school kids
who get into Oxford
on C grades...
because their mum
is a one-legged lesbian.
You don't know fuck all
about my grades.
Forgive me, I'm sure
you're highly educated.
Fire when ready.
How's that for
positive discrimination?
I want to thank
you both for listening...
and I really, really appreciate you
travelling all this way...
Your Royal Highness.
And you, too,
Prime Minister.
I think this is
quite brilliant.
It's absolutely brilliant.
You are completely crazy.
Don't touch--
Sorry, Your Royal Highness.
But you've got a
big role to play...
in getting the Scandinavian
region back on track.
You're popular,
inspirational...
and you have the power
to galvanize the people.
Now, whether you're
on board or not...
I'm going to
have to insist...
on getting you somewhere
I can ensure your safety.
How about you, Prime Minister?
You in or out?
Well, I think
it's about time...
that a politician did something that,
uh, actually made a difference.
Too true.
What?
Take her away.
Drink?
Why not?
Don't worry.
No harm will come
to the princess.
Well, I'm a
republican anyways,
so it really doesn't matter.|
Release the princess!
Okay, you're done.
Not so bad, right?
Hardly felt a thing.
Welcome aboard.
Pleasure is all mine.|
Ever heard of knocking?
Only when I'm casing
a place to rob.
Merlin said you
wanted to see me?
I hope J. B. 's training
is going as well as yours is.
Sit.
Congratulations on making it
to the final six candidates.
Your test results were even
better than I could've hoped.
Come in.
Ah.
Eggsy, I need to have
a private conversation.
You're dismissed.
Nonsense.
Let him observe.
Might learn
a thing or two.
As you wish.
Take a look at this.
Oh, for God's
sake, I've barely touched you.
Oh, man up!
Fucking hell!
That is rank, Harry.
You blew up his head?
It's a bit much, innit?
Actually, the explosion was
caused by an implant in his neck.
Here, under the scar.
Did my hardware pick up
the signal that triggered it?
Fortunately, yes.
Unfortunately, the IP address
I traced it to...
is registered
to the Valentine Corporation.
That's not much of a lead.
He has millions of
employees worldwide.
That Richmond Valentine
is a genius.
Did you not see
his announcement today?
No.
We each spend on average
$2,000 a year...
on cell phone
and internet usage.
It gives me great pleasure
to announce...
those days are over.
As of tomorrow...
every man, woman and child
can claim a free SIM card...
compatible with any cell
phone, any computer...
and utilize my communications
network for free.
Free calls...
free internet...
for everyone.
Forever.
Valentine's assistant
has the same implant scar.
I think Mr. Valentine and I
should have a t?e-?t?e.
He's having a
gala dinner next week.
I'll get you an invitation.
You need to be
careful, though.
Since you've been out, hundreds
of VIPs have gone missing.
No ransom notes,
exactly like Professor Arnold.
Then I suggest you make my alias
somebody worth kidnapping.
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
What, don't like heights?
Yeah, it's okay.
I've done it before, which is
probably why, come to think of it.
Hey, it's gonna be all right.
You're top of the class.
Listen up.
Your mission is to land in the target
without the radar detecting you.
If I read you on the radar, or you
miss the target, you go home.
Is that understood?
Drop zone coming up,
20 seconds.
We gotta go.
Eggsy, I really don't think
I can do this.
Of course you can't.
Head to the back
and I'll show you how, yeah?
Eggsy, wait! Hang on!
Roxy, just stop
fucking about!
Follow me, yeah?
Whoo!
Come on!
Roxy,
it's now or never.
Jump!
Good girl, Roxy...
I'm glad you made it!
Yeah!
Come on!
My, my, you're all
very cheerful.
Did you really think it was
gonna be that straightforward?
Any idiot can
read a heads-up display.
A Kingsman agent needs to be able
to solve problems under pressure.
Like what to do when one of
your group has no parachute.
What, no parachute?
Shit!
Who?
Fuck!
Which one?
What do we do?
I told you.
Aim for the target.
Come in under the radar.
And I hope not to be scraping
one of you up.
But if I do have to, and
you're inside the target...
please know I'll
be very impressed.
Fuck!
Oh, shit!
Everybody listen,
I've got a plan!
Pair off! Grab the
closest person to them.
Rufus, come on!
Oh, fuck!
Rufus!
Oh, shit! I can't!
Fuck!
Oh, thank God!
Rufus, you wanker!
Shit, we're an odd number now!
Quick, make a circle!
Fuck, he's right!
Boys, let's do it.
We pull our
cords one by one!
When we know who's fucked...
the person on
their right grabs them.
Okay, Eggsy.
Good plan, Eggsy.
You have 30 seconds.
Come on now, hurry.
Me first!
Oh, fuck!
Yes!
Okay, me next.
See you on the ground, boys.
Now me.
Fuck!
Roxy...
no matter what happens now,
I've got you, all right?
Okay, Eggsy. -
Yours first, okay?
Yep.
Oh, shit!
Shit!
Shit!|
Rox!
Fuck.
Hugo, Digby.
You don't land in the K,
you're not in the K.
Rufus,
you opened too soon.
You were all over
the radar.
All three of you,
pack your bags, go home.
Eggsy, Roxy,
congratulations.
You set a new record.
Opening at 300 feet...
that's pretty ballsy.
Well done for completing another task.
Fall out.
Sorry, sir.
But why the fuck did you
choose me as the gimp?
Am I the
expendable candidate?
No, no, no. You don't
talk to me like that.
You have a complaint, you come
here and you whisper it in my ear.
You need to take
that chip off your shoulder.
Mr. DeVere.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm awfully sorry. I seem to
have my dates muddled up.
Oh, no, no, no. I cancelled
the gala because of you.
Anybody willing
to donate that much...
deserves their own dinner.
Come in!
Thank you.
Got to admit, I was really
intrigued to meet you.
There aren't many
billionaires I don't know.
I don't doubt it.
And, obviously, I had my people
look into your affairs...
and that's some pretty
old money you're from.
How'd your folks make it?
Property, mostly.
Property and the markets.
Nothing questionable,
if that's your concern.
Look, I'm just into finding out
what caliber person you are.
I'm sure you
understand that.
I most certainly do.
Hope you're hungry.
I'm famished.
Good.
Grab a seat.
I'll have the Big Mac, please.
Great choice.
But nothing beats two
cheeseburgers with secret sauce.
Goes great with
this '45 Lafite.
A classic pairing.
And may I suggest Twinkies and a
1937 Ch?eau d'Yquem for pudding?
I like it.
So, you want to
donate to my foundation.
You are aware that I wound
things down in that area, right?
Climate change is a threat, which
affects us all, Mr. Valentine.
And you're one of the few powerful
men who seems to share my concerns.
No, I shut things down, because
I wasn't getting anywhere.
Every bit of research kept
pointing to the same thing.
That carbon emissions
are a red herring...
and that we're past the point of no return
no matter what remedial actions we take?
You know your shit.
I sometimes envy the blissful ignorance
of those less well versed in their...
"Shit. "
As Professor Arnold
always said...
"Humankind is the only virus
cursed to live...
"with the horrifying knowledge of
its host's fragile mortality. "
You know, not a lot of people
knew about him.
You like spy movies,
Mr. DeVere?
Nowadays, they're all a
little serious for my taste.
But the old ones...
Marvelous.
Give me a far-fetched
theatrical plot any day.
The old Bond movies.
Oh, man!
Oh, when I was a kid,
that was my dream job.
Gentleman spy.
I always felt the old Bond films
were only as good as the villain.
As a child, I rather fancied a
future as a colorful megalomaniac.
What a shame we both
had to grow up.
Bon app?it.
Just give me a couple of days
to think over your proposal.
I'll have my people
get in touch with yours...
and it's all good.
And thank you for
such a happy meal.
Well, want me
to follow him?
Nah.
I put a nano tracker gel
in the wine.
We'll know his every move
for the next 24 hours.
Finally find out
who he works for.
Valentine didn't let me
out of his sight.
All I got was this
on the way in.
South Glade Mission Church is a
hate group based in Kentucky.
FBI have been
monitoring them for years.
But you think Valentine
is a supporter?
No evidence yet of a direct
connection, but I'll keep looking.
Oh, by the way...
our ever-growing list of missing persons
now includes Scandinavian royalty.
Royal Crown Princess Tilde.
Just let me out,
you psycho!
I told you, you're free to go
any time you want.
As long as you agree
to my conditions.
I don't agree...
and I am never ever
going to agree!
Tough shit.
Bitch.
I want to speak
to the British Council!
The list of missing
celebrities and dignitaries
has continued to grow
in recent weeks...
and world leaders are coming under
increasing pressure to provide answers.
We are doing everything in our
power to find Princess Tilde.
You know, governments and
security forces worldwide. . .
Are working together to find the
person behind these abductions.
In other news,
people all over the world...
continue to wait in line day and
night to get their free SIM cards.
Mrs. P, did you get one?
Yeah, I've been
queuing up all day.
This unprecedented giveaway by
the philanthropist Richmond Valentine...
has already seen over a
billion cards distributed.
At ease.
So you thought we were done
for the day, huh?
Well, we're not.
A party?
Tonight, in London.
Who's this?
Your target.
Your mission is to use your
NLP training...
to win over the individual on the
photograph in your envelope.
And when I say
"win over"...
I do mean in
the biblical sense.
Easy.
Posh girls love
a bit of rough.
We'll see about that, yeah?
We certainly will.
Hi!
Sorry, I just had to come
over and say, amazing eyes.
Are you wearing
color contacts?
No!
You so are.
Oh, my God, negging!
That's hilarious.
I haven't heard anyone try that since
the noughties.
Excuse me?
"Negging"
Saying something negative to a pretty girl
in order to undermine her social value.
It's supposed to make you
want to win his approval.
Absurdly basic neuro-linguistic
programming technique.
Is it just me, or does this
champagne taste a little bit funny?
It's an acquired taste, mate.
I think it's just cheap.
Get one of these instead.
They're delicious.
If you're into seduction
techniques, this guy is textbook.
See what he just did?
It's called an opinion opener.
He got you talking
with a neutral question...
got all of us involved
in the conversation...
so that you craved
individual attention.
No, I'm just saying
the champagne tastes rank.
Lady Sophie
Montague-Herring.
Phone call for you
at reception.
Be right back. We'll see
you in a bit, yeah?
See you in a bit.
Budge up, Rox.
I'm feeling a bit rough.
Are you all right?
No.
MAN: Sorry to eavesdrop...
but there's a much easier way to
guarantee getting someone home.
Rohypnol.
Or even something stronger.
Who the fuck are you?
Where am I?
This knife...
can save your life, hmm?
Fuck!
My employer's got two
questions for you, Eggsy.
What the fuck is Kingsman?
And who's Harry Hart?
I don't know who
the fuck that is!
Shit!
Oh, Eggsy, I just killed two of your friends
who gave me the same bullshit answer!
Fuck!
Just cut the fucking ropes,
please!
MAN: Hey, Eggsy!
Is Kingsman worth dying for?
Fuck you!
Congratulations.
Bloody well done.
How did the others do?
Roxy passed
with flying colors.
Charlie's up next.
Want to watch?
Yeah, all right.
Is Kingsman really
worth dying for?
No, it fucking isn't!
Shit, I'll tell you
what you want. Please!
Chester King is Arthur.
Arthur's head of a spy agency.
It's called Kingsman.
Get me out of here!
Thank you, Charlie.
Much appreciated.
Come on!
That wasn't the fucking deal!
Fuck!
ARTHUR: I had such
high hopes for you.
You're a bloody disgrace.
Arthur, I'm sorry.
At least untie me.
Untie yourself.
Arthur, please.
I'm the fucking
son of the... Shit!
Anyone? Hello?
Galahad, Percival,
congratulations.
Your candidates have reached the
final stage of the testing process.
As tradition allows, you now have
24 hours to spend with them.
Eggsy, you should know your
father reached this point.
From now on...
there are no safety nets,
understood?
Good. Dismissed.
Charlie, time to go home.
Fuck you.
Fucking dad's gonna
hear about this!
"To pee or not to pee?"
That was the headline...
the day after I defused
a dirty bomb in Paris.
"Germany 1, England 5. "
Missed that game.
I was breaking up an undercover
spy ring at the Pentagon.
My first mission.
Foiled the assassination
of Margaret Thatcher.
Not everybody would
thank you for that one.
The point is, Eggsy, nobody
thanked me for any of them.
Front page news on all these
occasions was celebrity nonsense.
Because it's the nature of Kingsman
that our achievements remain secret.
A gentleman's name should appear
in the newspaper only three times.
When he's born, when he
marries, and when he dies.
And we are, first and
foremost, gentlemen.
That's me fucked then.
It's like Charlie said.
I'm just a pleb.
Nonsense.
Being a gentleman has nothing to do
with the circumstances of one's birth.
Being a gentleman
is something one learns.
Yeah, but how?
All right, first lesson.
You should've asked me
before you took a seat.
Second Lesson...
how to make
a proper martini.
Yes, Harry.
Goddamn it!
This fucking hurts!
You're the one who asked for
a biometric security system.
What's wrong with
a simple switch?
A simple switch?
This is an extremely
dangerous machine.
It should only be operated by someone
as responsible and sane as me.
Bad shit could happen if this
falls into the wrong hands.
Whoa!
We done here? Shit!
No. Now this one.
For the test at the church.
This one just
has a short range.
A simple switch will do.
So are you gonna teach
me how to talk proper,
like in My Fair Lady?
Don't be absurd.
Being a gentleman has nothing
to do with one's accent.
It's about being at ease
in one's own skin.
As Hemingway said,
"There is nothing noble...
"in being superior
to your fellow man.
"True nobility is being
superior to your former self. "
Now, the first thing every
gentleman needs is a good suit.
By which I mean, a bespoke suit.
Never off-the-peg.
And Kingsman suits
are always bulletproof.
So let's get you measured, and then,
whether you get the job or not...
you'll have a lasting and useful
memento of your time at Kingsman.
I'm so sorry, sir, but a gentleman
is completing his fitting.
Fitting Room Two
is available.
One does not use Fitting Room Two
when one is popping one's cherry.
Perhaps I'll show you Fitting
Room Three while we wait.
So we going up or down?
Neither.
Is this it?
Of course not.
Pull the hook on your left.
Oh, yes.
Very, very nice.
You're going to need a pair of
shoes to go with your suit.
An oxford is any formal shoe
with open lacing.
This additional decorative piece
is called broguing.
"Oxfords not brogues. "
Words to live by, Eggsy.
Words to live by.
Try a pair.
Your weapon scores
are excellent, by the way.
These you are familiar with, and
this is our standard issue pistol.
It's quite unique,
as you'll see.
It also fires
a shotgun cartridge
for use in messy
close-range situations.
How do they feel?
Yeah, good.
Now do your
very best impersonation...
of a German aristocrat's
formal greeting.
No, Eggsy-
That is sick.
In the old days, they had a
phone in the heel as well.
How do I get it back in?
Well, it's coated
in one of the
fastest acting neurotoxins
known to man...
so very carefully.
Now, I've had a
lot of fun with this.
One of our finest examples
of chemical engineering.
A poison,
harmless when ingested...
but at a time
convenient to you...
can be remotely activated.
Primed.
Lethal.
What about these?
What do these do?
Electrocute you?
Don't be ridiculous.
It's a hand grenade.
Shut up!
If you want to electrocute someone,
you'll need a signet ring.
A gentleman traditionally wears
the signet on his left hand.
But a Kingsman wears it on whichever
hand happens to be dominant.
Touch the contact
behind the ring...
it delivers 50,000 volts.
And what about them?
What makes them so special?
Nothing.
That technology has caught
up with the spy world.
Put it back, Eggsy.
Ah. Perfect timing.
The gentleman's
just finished.
Mr. DeVere!
What a coincidence.
You are totally
the reason I'm here.
When you left my house...
I was thirsting for that dope-ass
smoking jacket you had on.
And since I'm going
to Royal Ascot...
and, apparently, you need one
of these penguin suits...
here I am.
What are you doing here?
What's up, man?
Richmond Valentine.
This is my new valet. I was just
introducing him to my tailor.
Another coincidence.
So am I.
Have you had any chance to
think further on my proposal?
Most definitely.
My people will be getting
in touch with you very soon.
I guarantee it.
A word of advice.
Ascot requires top hat.
I might suggest
Lock and Co. Hatters.
Saint James's.
"Lox" as in smoked fish?
As in, "locked up. "
on.
I have trouble understanding
you people sometimes.
You all talk so funny.
Gentlemen, would you
look after him, please?
NOW this...
is a dope-ass top hat.
Gazelle, let's go ascoting.
Your hat looks fine, Gazelle.
Come on! Don't make me
late for the queen.
Come on, Gazelle!
We're gonna be late.
How far is Ascot?
How far?
Merlin said you
wanted to see me, sir?
Sit down.|
Pretty dog.
What's his name?
J. B.
As in "James Bond"?
No.
"Jason Bourne"?
No. "Jack Bauer. "
Oh!
Bravo.|
it pains me to admit it...
but I think that one day,
you might be as good a spy...
as any of them.
Take it.
Shoot the dog.
This weapon is live.
Give me the gun.
At least the girl's
got balls.
Get out.
I knew you
couldn't make it.
Go home.
Merlin, send in Roxy,
please.
Welcome to Kingsman...
Lancelot.
Mum!
Eggsy!
Oh, God.
Where have you been?
I've been so worried
about you.
Oh, my days.
Look how big you've grown!
Where is he?
I'm fine.
Eggsy, please,
just don't get involved.
No, I should never have
left you on your own.
This stops right now.
I'll be right back.
Eggsy.
Oi, Dean!
Oh, Mugsy,
so you're back.
What, you gone and nicked
a fucking taxi, now?
Yeah.
Can I have a word
about my mum's black eye?
You want to have a word with
me, you get out of that cab...
I'll knock you straight back down
on your fucking arse.
Tell your muppets to go inside,
then I'll get out.
Go on, lads.
It'll be two hits.
Me hitting him,
him hitting the floor.
Come on, then, you prick.
Let's see what you got.
Want a bit of me?
What are you doing?
No, no, no!
Get out of the fucking car!
What are you doing?
Where you going, you mug?
Go on, you got no bollocks!
Come on, Brut,
he hit my fucking mum!
Come back when you've
grown a pair!
Mugsy!
You throw away...
your biggest opportunity
over a fucking dog.
And then you humiliate me
by stealing my boss's car.
You shot a dog
just to get a fucking job.
Yes, I did.
And Mr. Pickle here reminds me of
that every time I take a shit!
You shot your dog
and had it stuffed?
You fucking freak.
No, I shot my dog...
and then I brought him home and
continued to care for him...
for the next 11 years
until he died of pancreatitis.
What?
It was a blank, Eggsy.
It was a fucking blank.
Remember Amelia?
Yeah.
She didn't drown.
She works in our tech department
in Berlin. She's fine.
Limits must be tested...
a Kingsman only condones the
risking of a life to save another.
Like my dad saved your life even though
your fuck-up cost his.
Or have you got him
stuffed here and all?
Can't you see that everything I've done
has been about trying to repay him?
Harry, listen to this.
Valentine is at last
saying something of note.
Do you know what
I love about pen and paper?
Nobody can hack
into this shit.
Our worldwide tour
was a complete success.
We have total coverall.
Like when all your numbers
in bingo are crossed out.
Bingo?
Bingo, the game.
You have played bingo, right?
Do I look like
I play bingo?
Point is...
if our tests go well at the church
tomorrow, we are good to go.
South Glade Mission Church.
Merlin, get the plane ready.
Will do.
Harry, I'm so sorry.
I'm gonna do whatever--
You should be.
You just stay right there. I'll
sort this mess out when I get back.
PREACHER: And I say to you...
bear witness!|
Watch the news.
AIDS!
Floods!
The blood of
the innocent, spilled!
And yet, there are those who
doubt this is the wrath of God.
Our filthy government condones
sodomy, divorce, abortion!
And yet, some still doubt...
this is the work
of the antichrist!
You do not have to be
a Jew, a nigger, a whore...
or an atheistic, science-loving
evolution spouter...
Charming sermon.
Can you see
Valentine anywhere?
So, my friends...
although he is a just God,
he is justly a vengeful one...
and there can be
no turning back...
from the almighty wrath...
Are you sure
we're out of range?
We're over 1,000 feet away.
What's wrong?
What if the calculations
are wrong?
You just have to trust me.
... Jew, nigger, fag lovers, and
the devil is burning them...
for all eternity.
Would you excuse me?
Where are you going?
Hey! What's your problem?
I'm a Catholic whore...
currently enjoying congress out of wedlock
with my black, Jewish boyfriend...
who works in a military
abortion clinic.
So, hail Satan...
and have a lovely
afternoon, madam.
Oh, shit.
He's leaving.
I'm starting the test now.
Let's hope enough of these
freaks have our SIM cards.
I kindly ask you
to sit down,
my friend!|
Just leave this church!
You just leave this church
like the infidel you are!
Satan cannot save you now!
You will eat your babies.
You will drown in the
blood of the Lord!
He will not save you!
Holy fuck!
Oh, shit, I can't watch this.
Get over here.
Lord, I can't change
Won't you fly high, free bird
Yeah
Jeez! Fuck.
Galahad,
can you hear me?
Harry!
Harry, what the heck
is going on?
Could you turn
the volume down, please?
I didn't expect it
to be that effective.
What kind of response
are we talking?
100 percent.
So,
everyone's been affected,
whether they have
a SIM card or not.
And we get the added benefit
of wiping out the Kingsman.
Not yet.
Oh, you need to see this.
What did you do to me?
I had no control.
I killed all those people.
I wanted to.
Clever, isn't it?
In simple terms,
it's a neurological wave...
that triggers the centers
of aggression...
and switches off
inhibitors.
Transmitted through your
nasty, free SIM cards,
I assume.
Do you know
what this is like?
It's like those old
movies we both love.
Now, I'm going to
tell you my whole plan...
and then I'm going to
come up
with some absurd and
convoluted way to kill you...
and you'll find an equally
convoluted way to escape.
Sounds good to me.
Well, this ain't
that kind of movie.
No!
Is he dead?
That tends to happen when you
shoot someone in the head.
It feels good, right?
No, no, it does not feel good.
It feels fucking awful.
What? You just killed how
many people in that church?
This is one guy.
No, no,
they killed each other.
Okay, send out
the countdown clock.
This party starts tomorrow.
Arthur?
Are you there?
Sadly, lam.
Assemble the Kingsmen.
Can't you see that
everything I've done
has been about
trying to repay him?
I see a young man
with potential...
who wants to do something
good with his life.
Arthur, Harry's dead.
Galahad is dead.
Hence, we have just drunk
a toast to him.
Well, then you know
what that psycho's doing.
How many people around the world
have got those SIM cards?
Valentine can send his signal
to any of them, all of them.
If they all go homicidal
at the same time then--
Indeed, and thanks
to Galahad's recordings...
we have Valentine's
confession.
The intelligence has been passed
on to the relevant authorities.
Our work is complete...
and a most
distinguished legacy
for our fallen friend,
it is, too.
And that's it?
Come sit down, boy.
This is an 1815
Napoleonic brandy.
And we only drink it
when we lose a Kingsman.
Galahad was very
fond of you.
And on this occasion...
I think it's acceptable for us
to bend the rules a little.
Are these all Kingsmen?
Yes, they're founder members.
I want you to join me
in a toast.
To Galahad.
Harry says you don't like
to break rules, Arthur.
Why now?
You're very good, Eggsy.
Perhaps I will make you my
proposal for Galahad's position.
Provided, of course,
that we can see eye to eye...
on certain
political matters.
Can you guess...
what this is?
I don't have to.
Harry showed me.
You click it. I die.
I thought that brandy
tasted a bit shit.
Bravo.
Valentine won you over,
somehow.
Once he explained,
I understood.
When you get a virus...
you get a fever.
That's the human body raising its
core temperature to kill the virus.
Planet Earth works
the same way.
Global warming is the fever.
Mankind is the virus.
We're making our planet sick.
A cull is our only hope.
If we don't reduce
our population ourselves...
there is only one of
two ways this can go.
The host kills the virus,
or the virus kills the host.
Either way...
The result is the same.
The virus dies.
So Valentine's gonna take care of
the population problem himself.
Well, if we don't do
something, nature will.
Sometimes a culling is the only way to
ensure that this species survives...
and history
will see Valentine...
as the man who saved
humanity from extinction.
And he gets to pick and choose
who gets culled, does he?
All his rich mates,
they get to live...
and anyone he thinks is worth
saving, he's keeping them safe...
whether they agree
with him or not.
And you, Eggsy.
In Harry's honor...
lam inviting you
to be part of a new world.
It's time to make
your decision.
I'd rather be with Harry.
Thanks.
So be it.
The problem with us
common types...
is that we're
light-fingered.
Kingsman's taught me a lot...
but sleight of hand...
Yes, they're
founder members.
I had that down already.
You dirty little fucking...
prick.
It's okay, Lancelot.
Put it down.
It's verified.
Arthur's phone is receiving update
texts about getting to safety.
We don't have a lot of time.
What are you going to do?
The question is,
what are we going to do?
God knows who's in Valentine's
pocket and who's not.
We have no choice.
We are gonna have to deal
with this ourselves.
Follow me.
What the fuck is this?
I have no idea.
What you're playing with...
is a prototype personal
transatmospheric vehicle.
It was developed as part of
Reagan's Star Wars project.
It's pretty basic,
but it should still work.
We're gonna take out
one of Valentine's satellites.
We're gonna break the chain,
stop the signal.
It'll take him a couple
of hours to reroute it...
which buys us enough time for you to
get me into Valentine's mainframe...
so I can shut it down.
Lancelot, you're going to
be using it.
Get into your halo suit.
Swedish Prime Minister,
requesting permission to land.
Permission granted.
Please.
Thank you.
How many more
are we expecting?
Not many.
Most have their own bunkers.
I figure we're just getting
the really nervous ones.
Welcome,
Prime Minister.
It seems the implant can
emit some kind of counter signal...
to ensure the wearer remains unaffected
by the waves from the SIM cards.
The waves that turn everyone
into a psycho killer.
Quite. But what he probably
didn't tell anyone...
is it can also super heat their
soft tissue at his command.
Valentine selected his chosen few
to get the countdown warning...
but he had to be sure they didn't
blab to the wrong people beforehand.
How does this help us
right now?
It doesn't.
Roxy, here we go!
The higher you go,
the more the balloons expand.
When you reach the edge
of the atmosphere...
they'll explode.
You'll need to deploy your
missile just before that, okay?
Edge of the atmosphere.
And once you've deployed, you'll
need to release for descent, fast.
Good luck.
You can do this, okay?
Yeah.
Eggsy, come on.
Time is not our friend.
You're getting in
on Arthur's invitation.
You're gonna need
to blend in.
I'm supposed to be Arthur?
His invitation is in his phone.
You give them this.
Give his real name,
Chester King.
What about you?
I'm your pilot.
I'm gonna stay here.
Is that gonna fit me?
A bespoke suit always fits.
Just be grateful
Harry had it made for you.
Get dressed.
What the fuck's wrong
with them?
I don't know. Could have something
to do with the mass genocide.
Give me the mic.
Hey-oh!
Everybody, listen up!
Hello, hello!
What the fuck is wrong
with you people?
I just wanna remind
you that today...
is a day of celebration.
We must put aside
all thoughts of death...
and focus on birth.
The birth of a new age.
We mustn't mourn those
who give their lives today.
We should honor
their sacrifice...
Has she got my number to call me back?
I got a new phone.
... and their roles...
... in saving the human race.
We must put aside
doubt and guilt.
You are the chosen people.
When folks tell their kids
the story of Noah's Ark...
is Noah the bad guy?
CROWD: No!
ls God the bad guy?
How about the animals
marching two by two?
CROWD: No!
Of course not!
Yeah, that's it!
Let's turn those frowns
upside down.
Eat, drink...
and party!
And I will see you all
in the new age.
Rox, it's me.
How's the view?
Hideous
Mine's pretty sweet.
They made you one
of these suits yet?
No, not yet.
You've got something to
look forward to then.
We're coming up on Valentine's base.
Gotta go.
Good luck.
Looking good, Eggsy.
Feeling good, Merlin.
This is
November-2-4-7-Charlie-Kilo. . .
Requesting permission to land.
Permission is granted.
Fuck me.
Mmm-hmm.
599531, we're on.
Chester King.
Mr. King, welcome.
I'm sure you've adhered to Valentine's
strict no-weapons policy...
but if you don't object...
Of course.
Thank you.
Do you have any luggage?
Congratulations, Mycroft,
you just graduated
from my pilot to my valet.
You cheeky--
Understood?
Good.
Thank you.
Eggsy,
find a laptop, get me online.
The clock is ticking.
And remember, try to blend in.
Would sir care
for a drink?
Martini.
Gin, not vodka, obviously.
Stirred for 10 seconds while glancing
at an unopened bottle of vermouth.
Thank you.
Merlin,
are you clocking this?
Yes, I am. Stay focused.
Lancelot, you're doing great.
Not much further to go.
Yes, Merlin.
Eggsy, get me online now.
Yep, I'm on it.
Lancelot, you're approaching
your altitude limit.
Those balloons
won't last much longer.
Prepare to engage missile.
Society's dead.
Long live society.
Amen to that.
I'm Morten Lindstr?.
Chester King.
How'd you get online?
I couldn't.
Oh, well, it's a closed
network, you see.
Pre-authorized
connections only.
Ah.
I've got a fix
on the satellite.
Do you have
the correct time?
I think I'm still
in my last time zone.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Let's see now.
Eggsy, I'm in.
Get your arse back
to the plane, now.
On my way.
Lancelot, good luck!
Firing in 3... 2...
Nice and slow.
Fuck are you doing here?
Well, my family
were invited, obviously.
Now, get the fuck up!
Slowly.
Oh, shit. Lancelot,
hurry up and fire!
That other balloon
is gonna blow!
Yes, Merlin. I've nearly got it.
Give me a second!
Valentine!
I've caught a fucking spy!
V-Glass, zoom.
Oh, fuck!
It's that young valet.
Son of a bitch.
GO!' it!
Oh, shit.
Sound the alarm!
I'm not taking any chances.
Okay, you send out
the two-minute warning.
I'm starting the override.
All right, let's do this.
Countdown initiated.
You see him?
Right here.
Eggsy, take a left.
Two guards, up ahead.
Lancelot! Release now!
Eggsy,
straight ahead, then right.
There's two more.
AH right,
everybody on your feet!
Countdown to V-day!
Welcome in the new age!
Flat spin.
Eggsy, next left,
down the narrow tunnel!
Here we go!
10...
9...
8...
7...
6...
5...
4...
3...
2...
1!
Nice! Well done,
both of you.
It's not working!
It's supposed to be working!
What the fuck?
Yes!
Well done, Roxy. Good girl.
We've lost one
of our satellites.
Oh, no, no. There's no way
I can hack past that.
What's going on?
Is there a problem?
Come on.
There's no need for guns.
I'm just a pilot.
Oh, fuck. Merlin!
Get in here!
Come on!
Let's get the fuck
out of here!
We can't.
I can't get into
Valentine's machine.
He's got biometric security.
You're gonna have
to get in there
and make sure his hand
never touches that desk.
Are you taking
the fucking piss?
I'm afraid not.
Let's have that then.
Uh-uh.
This is mine.
I'll show you yours.
Good choice.
How long to re-link
the satellite chain?
It'll take an hour,
maybe two.
Bullshit! Just bring these two
closer together.
But that's not yours.
V-Glass, call E-man.|
E, it's V.
Listen, man, I got a
little hiccup on this end.
I need to piggyback.
One of my satellites
just went down,
but it's right next
to one of yours.
You read my mind.
How long before you
make that happen?
Go.
All right, we should be
coming back online.
10 percent.
Oh, shit!
Eggsy, Valentine's using
someone ease뭩 satellite.
He's going to
reconnect the chain.
It's going to take him
no time at all.
It's at 20 percent.
Eggsy, it seems Valentine's got a
present for you. Get a move on!
Is that Kingsman kid dead yet?
Not yet,
but he will be soon.
Good.
Merlin, I'm fucked.
As am I.
They're coming at me from both sides.
I'm out of options.
Rox, I need a favor.
Call my mum.
Tell her to lock herself
away from Dean.
And the baby...
and tell her I love her.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Merlin, remember those implants
you said were of no use to us?
Any chance you can
turn them on?
All right.
My turn to play, Valentine.
Oh, no!
What the fuck is he doing?
I can't stop this.
Yes, please.
No!
oh, my God!
That is fucking spectacular!
Merlin,
you're a fucking genius!
What the fuck
is happening out there?
Aren't you that princess
who went missing?
Can you get me out?
If I do, will you
give me a kiss?
I've always wanted
to kiss a princess.
If you get me out right now, I'll
give you more than just a kiss.
You motherfucker.
Did you really think
I was stupid enough...
to implant one of those
things in my own head?
What are you, fucking crazy?
All those innocent people
killed and for what?
You didn't stop shit!
Fine, I've locked the door.
What do you want me to do now?
As I said, put your daughter in the
bathroom and throw away the key.
It's still happening!
You're fucking insane!
Just do it.
Eggsy,
the signal's started!
Get Valentine's hand off
that bloody desk now!
Sorry, love.
Got to save the world.
If you save the world...
we can do it in the asshole.
I'll be right back.
Good luck!
London.
Rio.
Get down!
You did it!
The glass is not
gonna hold long.
You stay here.
Merlin, quickly,
how do I get up there?
Keep shooting, I'll find a route.
Understood.
Holy fuck!
We're back up.
We're back up!
This is great!|
Eggsy!
Fucking get on with it!
Kick his ass, Gazy!
Baby, give it up
Give it up
Seoul, Caracas, Mumbai!
Baby, give it up
Give it up
Kill that motherfucker!
He killed all our friends!
Eggsy, the world is
going to shit!
Is he dead yet?
Not yet!
Stop playing
with your food!
Kill him!
Gazelle!
Come on! Come on!
Kill him!
Hey!|
Well done, son!
Whoo! Yes!
Yes, Eggsy!
Well done, Eggsy!
And you, Lancelot.
I'm so sorry.
Mummy would never hurt you.
Are you okay?
Harry would be
proud of you, Eggsy.
He was right.
What's up, man?
Is this the part where you
say some really bad pun?
Well, it's like
you said to Harry.
This ain't that kind
of movie, Brut.
Perfect.
Eggsy, where are
you going?
There's no need for champagne.
We got loads in the plane.
Did you save
the world?
Yes, I did.
So, you gonna come in?
Yes, lam.
Slave to love
Merlin, the cell's locked.
How do I get in?
26-25.
Merlin, you're the guvnor.
You owe me, Eggsy.
Eggsy?
Oh.
Oh, my word.
The storm is breaking
Or so it seems
We're too young to reason
Too grown up to dream
Now spring is turning
Your face to mine
I can hear your laughter
I can see your smile
Slave to love
I can't escape
I'm a slave to love
Slave to love
Michelle, turn that shit off.
It's doing my nut in.
I rather like that song.
Leave it on, eh, Mum
Mugsy's back.
You've finally come to have that
word with me, have you, son
Or are you gonna
run away again...
and pretend you're going to
court, dressed like that
Oh, you mean this
No.
I know this bloke who's just taken
over a tailor shop on Savile Row.
He's given me a job, Mum.
It comes with a lot of perks.
Including a house.
Come and live
with me there, Mum.
Come on.
Sit down, you.
Only place she'll be visiting
is you in fucking hospital.
Do you hear Just
leave him alone, Dean!
Eggsy, just go.
Please, just go, babe.
All right.
That's it,
do as Mummy says.
Why don't you ask
that tailor friend of yours,
and knock up a
nice chicken costume.
It'll suit you, you mug.
As a good friend
once said...
"Manners...
"market...
"man. "
Dean
Shut the fuck up.
Eggsy, I'm gonna shove
your manners up your fucking--
So...
are we gonna stand around here
all day, or are we gonna fight
Get ready for it
You said whatever
you put out there
Whatever you put out there
ls gonna come back
You said whenever
you are ready
Whenever you are ready
Just let it all out
I know 'cause the
enemy inside me
'Cause the enemy inside me
is holding me back
But we know there's
something in the silence
There's something
in the silence
Get ready for it
You said there's
only place left to find
Together we can
save the world tonight
Get ready for it
You said every
life is a lesson
Are you a fool or a kingsman
'Cause only you know
Hold on, 'cause the
volume is rising
Yeah, the volume is rising
So you better hold on
The night is young
Until it's over,
until it's over
The night is young
The night is ours
Until tomorrow, until tomorrow
Get ready for it
Yeah, get ready for it
You said there's
only one place left to find
Together we can
save the world tonight
Get ready for it
The night is young
Until it's over
The night is ours
Until tomorrow
Get ready for it
I'll hold your hand
With good intentions
The night is ours
Until tomorrow
You said there's
only one place left to find
Together we can
save the world tonight
Get ready for it
Life been crazy
All advice has
been to chill more
Ironic I've been living off
with people down to kill for
And I find no comfort
in numbers
Knowin' there's
always a mil more
Fact was that cat
dragged my pretty...
Right at the top
of that billboard
And all of my folks
who done been here from jump
You the ones
I 'ma cover the bill for
And as I get ill more
We gon' triple the order
of champagne and spill more
Let's settle the real score
Been wondering
what the public gotta feel for
So let's keep it real, yeah
You know I'm killing game
as soon as I step on the field
Y'all at the top
are all mad now
There's no turning back now
I won't ever back down
They feel me like
they giving Ciggy a pat down
I needed a moment
I found it
Lately I've been
on my runnin' the town shit
Especially walkin' around with
This heavy crown
You can't always
please the crowd
But I am still not bowing down
This heavy crown
It comes and goes around
And when it's time
I'll pass it proud
But... l got it now
So keep it cute, chick
And don't be hatin'
on the new chick
Go back and check your stats
And bet they let you
know I do's this
Glasses full of empty
Depending on
point of view chick
If you was mad before
I bet you hate me
for this new shit
Maybe you should watch
What you've got
coming out your two lips
Get cool with how I kick it
Or else you gon'
get the boot...
Ciggy A-z-A
AKA captain
of the crew ship
Don't penny pinch
I promise, babe,
I don't need your two cents
Get rid of the makeup
Let us see just who you is
But if you feel like that girl
Bless your heart
Go get it how you live
When you hear my name
You gotta know
that she's something regal
I'm one of one
Ain't no sequels
I'm wearing
This heavy crown
You can't always
please the crowd
But I am still not bowing down
This heavy crown
It comes and goes around
And when it's time
I'll pass it proud
But... l got it now
To everyone who said
I'd never make it
Oh, Lord, weren't you mistaken
I got a dinner date
with greatness
liggy lgg ain't never been
nothin' to play wit, hold up
To everyone who said
I'd never make it
I'm at the top
Laughin' at you faces
I've been
practicing my patience
But I switch back quick
If you play with
This heavy crown
To everyone who said
I'd never make it
This heavy crown
Oh, Lord, weren't you mistaken
To everyone who said
I'd never make it
This heavy crown
I'm at the top
Laughin' at you faces
But... l got it now